你可曾想过在Google Play上
Have you ever wondered how some developers
开发者是如何构建出很棒的项目和公司
build a great product and business on Google Play
我是Serge Kassardjian
My name is Serge Kassardjian.
在Google Play小组工作
I work on the Google Play team.
我专注于Android生态系统的应用和游戏
My focus is on apps and games for our Android ecosystem.
我讲告诉你如何在Play上开发一个成功的应用
I'm going to tell you how to create a successful app in Play
并且教你如何应用独特的Android性能来做到这些
and leverage unique Android features to do so.
我们小组齐心协力来创建良好的安卓体验
My team works with our partners to build great experiences
让他们的内容安装在
for Android that get their content distributed
全世界大量的安卓用户手机上
to our large install base of Android users around the world.
我们想帮你的企业和品牌在Google Play上取得成功
We want your business and brand to succeed on Google Play.
那么  你将在这里学到什么
So what will you learn here
我将向你展示如何在Play上创建一个成功的应用
I will show you how to create a successful app in Play
以及充分利用Android独有的特性
and leverage unique Android features to do so.
有很多不错的办法来体现价值
There are a lot of great ways to unlock value
并成为一个成功的Android开发者
and succeed as an Android developer.
我将帮你入门
And I will help you get started doing so.
我将向你展示怎么做和为什么要这么做
I'm going to show you how and why to do this,
向你的品牌和企业展示它的重要性
demonstrating its importance to your brand and business.
我也将向你展示有趣的Android方面的知识
I'll also show you some interesting Android related
以及一些你可能不了解的产品特性
facts as well product features you may not be aware of.
Google Play是一个很好的地方来壮大你的企业
Google Play is a great place to grow your business,
特别当你做对了的时候
especially if you do it the right way.
这个平台正在迅速发展
The platform is growing very quickly
随着我们受众在这个商店中
as is our engaged audience interacting
通过应用和游戏的互动
with the apps and games in the store.
我们现在有超过500亿的下载量
We currently have over 50 billion downloads,
并且每个月有超过20亿的下载量
with over 2 billion downloads coming every month,
与2012年相比  在2013年我们支付给开发者的钱
and we've paid out more than 4x as much money to developers
是原来的4倍以上
in 2013 as we did compared to 2012.
Google Play同时提供了一个独特的迭代环境
Play also provides a unique iterative environment
对于开发者允许A/B测试
for our developers that allows them to A/B test
有了这样一个特性  alpha和beta测试以后再发布
using such features as alpha and beta testing and staged roll outs.
此外  开发者可以利用其他形式的特性
Further, developers can take advantage of other form factors
通过其他的渠道推动参与
that will drive engagement through new channels
比如平板  穿戴式设备或者其他
and touch points such as tablets, wearables, and others.
这是一个很棒的方式来给你的应用进行新的测试
This is an awesome way to drive new use cases for your app that
之前是行不通的  如果你的应用是只在智能手机上跑
previously were not available when you were on smartphones only.
Play不仅让你利用我们庞大的用户
Play will not only allow you to leverage our gigantic audience,
同时也利用新的功能使用你的内容
but also take advantage of new functionality using your content.
我们生活在一个日益全球化的世界
We are living in an increasingly global world,
每个企业和应用都将变得国际化
and every business and app is becoming an international one.
你的全球化战略是什么
What is your strategy across the globe
Google Play和Android是一个很好的机会
Google Play and Android is an opportunity
来打开这个大门  通过在各种不同的市场上
to unlock this through our distribution and strengths
我们的发行量之大和力量增长之快
in various markets that are large and growing quickly
你可以在这里看到
as you can see here.
我的合作伙伴比如JackThreads和Noom
Partners such as JackThreads and Noom
都用这个工具来扩展国际用户
all use tools to grow international numbers.
事实上2/3的Play上的购买都是跨国的
In fact, 2/3 of all Play purchases actually happen internationally.
并且我们强烈鼓励我们的开发者利用好这一点
And we strongly encourage our developers to take advantage of this.
这个庞大的国际组织
This large international community
包括了200多个国家能从中下载内容
includes 200 plus countries that can download from the Play
在130多个消费者市场
store at 130 plus buyer markets.
为了能利用好这个大好机会
To take advantage of this big opportunity,
用我们的工具来实现国际化
use our tools for internationalization
以及语言翻译来实现从国家到国家
and language translation to help make shifting from country
和s语言到语言的转换都很容易
to country and language to language very easy.
用户更能被你的应用所吸引
Users will feel a lot more attached to your app
如果这让他感到熟悉而非陌生
if it feels familiar and not so foreign.
此外  一些你不在的特定的国家
Further, identify countries that you are not
也将是潜在的Android和Play的巨大市场
in that are potentially great markets for Android and Play.
你可以看到意料之外的道路上的问题
You can see unexpected spikes of traffic
在那些你已经开始运作的国家里
in countries that you've activated,
然后你开始关注那些与Android和Play大市场
and start focusing on those markets, which
一致的市场
coincide with the big markets for Android and Play.
接下来你要考虑的事情是设计
The next thing to look at is design.
我无法表述好的视觉设计
I can't express the importance of good visual design
和交互模式的重要性
and interaction patterns.
设计  设计  还是设计
Design, design, design.
打造一个好用的Android设计
Make a strong Android Design.
它能颠覆一切
It changes everything.
人们喜欢好看的应用
People love great looking apps.
这是你品牌的延伸
It's your extension of your brand.
纯粹的Android设计使你与你的用户用一种
Pure Android Design makes you speak to the audience in a way
设备交互的方式对话
that they are used to interacting with their device.
这会改进你的内容的表达  并且把最合适的内容放在最前面
It will improve conversion and bring your right content to the front.
好的设计的应用就是好用的应用
Great Design apps are great performing apps.
那么  设计为什么以及怎么起作用的呢
So why and how does Design help
当然  质量永远是第一位的
Well, quality wins every time.
我们的研究人员展示了
Our researchers have shown that users
用户愿意给更好的质量付费
are willing to pay more for better quality.
通过使用我们的Android设计指南
By using our Android Design guidelines,
比如我们标准的动作栏  下拉菜单  标签
such as our standard action bar, drawer, and tabs,
你可以创建一个环境
you can create an environment that people
让用户能花更多的时间或钱  觉得
will spend more and feel like it's
这是你的内容最好的表达方式
the primary channel for your content.
正如你所见的  当你的评分星级上升时
As you can see here, as your star rating improves,
你的用户更愿意付钱
so does consumer's willingness to pay.
我们看到一个巨大的人均消费量的增长
We see a dramatic increase in monetization per user
随着星级从一星到五星
as ratings move from one to five stars.
此外  平板优化强调  大小  质量  和消费
Further, tablet optimization emphasizes sizes quality and purchases.
和手机端比较  我们能看到在平板上有1.7倍的购买率
Compared to phones, we've seen a 1.7 next purchase
rate on tablets.
同时  我们继续让你的客户更方便的购买
Also, we continue to make it much easier
随着我们对支付方式支持的增长
for your customers to pay as we increase our forms of payment.
举个栗子  直接的账单购买
For example, direct carrier billing
支持超过50%的用户数量。
is now available for over 50% of Play users.
别忘了  你可以回应所有评论
And don't forget, you can respond to all your reviewers.
与用户交流来提升你的星级以改良应用
Talk to your audience to get your ratings up and improve your app.
随着用户看到你与他们互动
As your audience sees you interacting with them
并且对他们的需求上投资
and invested in their needs, they'll
他们会给出有价值的反馈
provide valuable feedback and consider
并且考虑基于你的改变来改变他们的评论
changing their review based on your changes.
这不光帮你提升了你的应用质量
Not only does this help you improve your app,
也最终帮助改良了这个社区
but ultimately helps improve the community
中你的应用和用户对你公司感觉的互动
of interacting around your app and their feelings
towards your company.
别忘了  合适的大小也起着重要的作用
And don't forget-- sizing correctly makes a big difference.
你的应用越小
The smaller your app, the less likely people
用户越不容易删掉它  并且也更愿意下载它
will uninstall it, and more likely they will to download it.
人们期待这样的东西
People look for this stuff.
他们不想应用吞食他们的内存空间
They don't want apps that eat up their memory
耗干他们的电池
and drain their battery.
这些方法都有助于减少卸载率
There are ways to reduce these uninstalls.
卸载会最终的伤害你的应用
Uninstalls will ultimately hurt you
在商店里的出现和搜索结果
in how you appear in the charts and search in the store.
记住要避免应用被卸载
Always try to avoid these uninstalls.
别忘了  利用好所有我们
And don't forget, take advantage of all
有趣的特点  独特的Android特性和最好的实践练习
of our fun, unique Android features and best practices.
惊艳的图标会抓住每个人的注意力
Standout icons catch everyone's attention,
并且Android图标有一个用户期待的显著模式
and Android icons have a distinct style that our users look for.
这些应用有着在清晰背景下的轮廓
The app should be a silhouette on a clear background
有着高的分辨率
at a high definition, XXHDP.
确保你的应用对于设备进行了优化
Make sure yours is optimized for devices
并且你应用有一个有效的识别方式
and is an effective identifier of your app.
确保Play对它的分类准确
Make a great Play listing that is very accurate
并且要包括在手机和平板上的应用截图
and includes screenshots of both phone and tablets
并且给这个列表里创建一个好的视频
as well as creating a great video for this listing.
当你的应用上市的时候  创建一个Google Play徽章
When you are marketing your app, create a Google Play badge
在你的材料里面并且做一个链接
on your materials and deep link it
连到Play商店你的应用列表  这样你的用户能更简单的找到你的应用
to your Play store listing so your users can find your app easily.
最后  别忘了给你的应用增加一些乐趣
And finally, don't forget to have some fun with your app
并且支持消费者在新的或者现有的方式来用
and engage your consumers in new and exciting ways using
动态消息  实时壁纸  或者用好玩的小部件
dynamic notifications, live wallpapers, and creative widgets.
感谢您花时间来学习
Thank you for taking the time to learn more
关于这些最好的Google Play上的应用和游戏实例
about some of the best practices for apps and games on Google Play.
我们期待看到你的新版本应用
We are excited to see the new version of your app.
我是Serge  期待着
My name is Serge, and I'm looking forward
与优秀的应用开发者一起工作
to working with some great app developers.